A Finding Aid to the Dorothy Weiss Gallery Records, circa 1964-2001 (bulk 1984-2000), in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Dorothy Weiss Gallery records
circa 1964-2001
bulk 1984-2000
Archives of American Art
Dorothy Weiss Gallery
AAA.doroweig
Archival Resource Key
18.7 Linear feet
The records of the Dorothy Weiss Gallery measure 18.7 linear feet and date from circa 1964 to 2001 (bulk 1984-2000). The collection documents the gallery's relationships with approximately three hundred artists, through artist files, exhibition files, and subject files, and is an excellent source of information on the work of contemporary ceramic and glass sculptors.
Historical Note
Dorothy Weiss founded the Dorothy Weiss Gallery in 1984. From 1977 Weiss had partnered with Sue Meyer and Virginia Breier in Meyer Breier Weiss Contemporary Crafts, Inc. She opened her new gallery in what was to be its permanent location at 256 Sutter Street in downtown San Francisco.
The Dorothy Weiss Gallery was renowned in San Francisco for the quality of its crafts program and the artists it represented. Weiss focused on contemporary ceramic and glass sculpture with an emphasis on non-functional, sculptural work. She also showed some paintings, drawings and monotypes, and her interests in this area expanded, particularly in the mid-1990s, when she began exhibiting works by artists such as Daniel Brice, in addition to showing drawings by artists generally known for their sculpture.
Weiss represented many of the country's most prominent and well-respected artists working in glass, including Hank Murta Adams, Dale Chihuly, Richard Marquis, William Morris, Jay Musler, Clifford Rainey, Italo Scanga, Therman Statom, and James Watkins. Glass exhibitions at the gallery included site-specific installations by artists such as Statom, Adams, and Rainey.
The gallery was also an important venue for contemporary ceramists such as Rudy Autio, Annette Corcoran, Ruth Duckworth, Michael Lucero, Beverly Mayeri, and Robert Turner. Monthly exhibitions were held on the Third floor with the Fourth floor gallery space being reserved for a variety of work by gallery artists. "Teapot Invitationals," and exhibitions of "new glass" featuring teapots and glass sculpture by a variety of artists were held regularly at the gallery.
Weiss was an active participant in the wider art community, hosting collector's groups from around the country and guests during conferences, such as a special Glass Invitational in conjunction with the Glass Art Society Conference in March 1994. As a member of the San Francisco Art Dealers Association (SFADA), Weiss participated in First Thursday, holding opening receptions to new exhibitions on the first Thursday of every month and often accompanying them with artists' talks. She also participated in an annual Introductions show along with other SFADA members, representing younger, emerging artists in the Bay Area and nationwide. In addition, Weiss assisted the American Craft Museum in developing its exhibition programs, and was a Collectors Circle Affiliate for the American Craft Council.
Dorothy Weiss closed the gallery in 2000, retiring at the age of eighty. On October 4 of that year the Museum of Craft and Folk Art in San Francisco opened A Tribute to Dorothy Weiss, an exhibition selected from her own collection.
Scope and Content Note
The Dorothy Weiss Gallery records measure 18.7 linear feet and date from circa 1964 to 2001 (bulk 1984-2000). Although the collection includes limited records overlapping from Weiss's dealings with some artists through Meyer Breier Weiss Contemporary Crafts, Inc., its primary focus is the activities of the Dorothy Weiss Gallery. The records provide fairly extensive coverage of the gallery's relationship with approximately thirty artists, and scattered documentation of Weiss's relationship with more than two hundred other artists whose work she represented, exhibited, or had an interest in at some time during the gallery's existence. Overall, the collection is an excellent source of information on contemporary ceramic and glass sculpture and includes artist files of correspondence, administrative records, printed matter, and photographic material, as well as exhibition files and subject files.
The bulk of the collection consists of Series 1: Artist Files, which includes correspondence with artists, biographical material, printed material relating to exhibitions at the Dorothy Weiss Gallery and elsewhere, photographs of artwork, and administrative records such as price lists, inventories, and loan and consignment documentation.
Series 2: Exhibition Files contains records of approximately twenty-five group exhibitions held at the gallery, such as the Teapot Invitationals, and various exhibitions of glass artists. Records relating to exhibitions for a single artist's work can be found in Series 1: Artist Files.
Series 3: Subject Files consists of a small group of general subject files maintained by the gallery, such as correspondence with different types of clients, and records relating to specific projects outside the gallery in which Weiss participated.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into three series. The basic original arrangement was maintained throughout the collection. Records are generally arranged alphabetically by artist, subject, or exhibition, and then chronologically.
Missing Title
Series 1: Artist Files, circa 1964-2001(boxes 1-18, OV 21; 17.5 linear ft.)
Series 2: Exhibition Files, 1979-1999 (box 19; 0.75 linear ft.)
Series 3: Subject Files, 1983-2000 (boxes 19-20; 0.45 linear ft.)
Provenance
The collection was donated to the Archives of American Art by Dorothy Weiss in 2002.
Restrictions on Access
The collection is open for research. Use requires an appointment and is limited to the Washington, D.C. research facility.
Art galleries, Commercial -- California; Glass art; Ceramics; Handicraft; Weiss, Dorothy, 1921-; Meyer Breyer Weiss Contemporary Crafts, Inc.; Meyer, Sue, 1913-; Nanette L. Laitman Documentation Project for Craft and Decorative Arts in America; Breier, Virginia, 1927-
- Artist Files, circa 1964-2001; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 17.5 Linear feet Boxes 1-18, OV 21
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains files for artists represented by the gallery, or featured in the gallery's exhibitions. There are also files for artists in whom Weiss had an interest but with whom she never pursued a business relationship. While some artists are represented by only a single file, others are represented more fully. The latter include Hank Murta Adams, Rudy Autio, Annette Corcoran, Philip Cornelius, Wouter Dam, Ruth Duckworth, Jack Earl, Tony Hepburn, Jun Kaneko, Michael Lucero, Beverly Mayeri, William Morris, Jay Musler, Barbara Bell Smith, Statom Therman, Yoshio Taylor, Robert Turner, Jamie Walker, and Stan Welsh.
  Files typically include any or all of the following: announcements and press releases for exhibitions held at the gallery; correspondence with artists, buyers, collectors, museums and art institutions; biographical material such as résumés and artist statements; consignment, loan and shipping records; inventories and price lists; printed material; photographs of artists; and photographs of artwork.
  Correspondence generally includes original incoming letters and drafts or copies of outgoing letters. To preserve the original order of the collection, records relating to a particular artist were broken down according to the system imposed by the creator. Consequently, files labeled "correspondence" may also include material such as price lists, inventories, consignment and loan records, invoices, and shipping records.
  Photographic material generally consists of images of artwork and may also contain images of gallery installations or photographs of work in an artist's studio. Photographs of artists are filed separately and/or noted in the container list.
  Additional slide transparencies of artwork by many of the artists represented here can be found at the end of the series. These were separated from the artist files in which they were originally housed for storage reasons. Researchers should check the list of transparencies for additional information about any artist of interest. "SB" next to the box number indicates the slide box in which particular slide transparencies are housed.
  Arrangement note
  Files are arranged alphabetically by artist. When there is more than one folder for an artist they are arranged alphabetically by folder title, with the exception of photographs of artists and photographic material which are placed at the end of each group. Transparencies of artwork are arranged alphabetically by artists, and chronologically by date of artwork (not the date that the transparency was developed which is often unknown), with undated transparencies at the beginning of each group.
  - Abilgard, Mark, Archival Resource Key (Box 1)
    - General, 1989-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Printed Material, 1989-1998, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abright, Bill, General, 1987-1999, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Adams, Hank Murta, Archival Resource Key (Box 1)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1985-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Collector Records, 1993-1997, undated, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Consignment Records, 1991-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
    - Loan Forms, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Printed Material, 1985-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Shipping Records, 1989-1997, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Photographs of Adams, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1981-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 13-15)
  - Aebersold, Jane Ford, General, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Alexandrov, Simona, General, circa 1994-1996, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Anderson, Daniel, General, 1987-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Anderson, Marvin, General, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Andreson, Laura, General, 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Arima, Curtis, General, 1997-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Arleo, Adrian, General, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Autio, Rudy, Archival Resource Key (Box 1)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1985-1998, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Biographies, Résumés, 1995, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Collector Records, 1992-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Consignment Records, 1991-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Consignment Records (other galleries), 1988-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 28-31)
    - Correspondence, Gallery Koyanagi, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Printed Material, 1983-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 33-34)
    - Shipping Records, 1987-1997, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Photographs of Autio, 1987-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Photographic Material, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Photographic Material, cont., 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Balas, Jack, General, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bartneck, Lea and Richard Marquis, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bean, Kevin, General, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Berman, Harriete Estel, General, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bermudez, Luis, General, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Blakely, Ellen, General, 1983-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bongers, Jaap, Archival Resource Key (Box 2)
    - General, 1987-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1987-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Bowers, Jack, General, circa 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Bradford, Steven P., General, 1995-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Braun, Stephen, General, circa 1990-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Brice, Daniel, General, 1991-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bright, Erik, General, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Briscoe, Steve, Archival Resource Key (Box 2)
    - General, 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Britt, John, General, 1995-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Brook-Kothlow, Ingrid, General, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Burleson, Mark, General, 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Carlson, Robert, circa 1987-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Carman, Nancy, Archival Resource Key (Box 2)
    - General, 1982-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1973-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Cartwright, Virginia, General, 1981-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Castle, Wendell, General, 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Caswell, James, Photographic Material, circa 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Cecula, Marek, General, circa 1991-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Chamberlin, Scott, Archival Resource Key (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 28-31)
    - Printed Material, 1980-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Chardiet, Jose, General, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Chihuly, Dale, Archival Resource Key (Box 2)
    - General, 1991-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Christenson, Ann, General, 1990-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Chung, Sam, General, 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Clayman, Daniel, General, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Cohen, Carol, 1988-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Corcoran, Annette, Archival Resource Key (Box 3)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1984-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Biographies and Résumés, 1990-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Collector Records, 1990-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Corcoran Catalog, 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1984-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8-11)
    - Loan Records, 1990-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 12-13)
    - Price Lists, 1991-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Printed Material, 1982-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
    - Photographs of Corcoran, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18-21)
  - Philip Cornelius, Archival Resource Key (Box 3)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1982-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 23-24)
    - Printed Material, 1976-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 26-28)
  - Corney, Michael, General, circa 1993-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Cox, Kris, Archival Resource Key (Box 3)
    - General, 1984-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Czeresko, Deborah, General, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Dam, Wouter, Archival Resource Key (Box 3)
    - Correspondence, circa 1995-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 33-34)
    - Printed Material, circa 1995-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - da Silva, Marilyn, General, 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Daunell, David, General, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Daw, Deidre, General, circa 1992-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - de la Torre, Einar and Jamex, General, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Delisle, Roseline, Archival Resource Key (Box 4)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Photographic Material, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Printed Material, 1983-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Deller, Harris, General, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - de Swart, Peter, Archival Resource Key (Box 4)
    - General, 1991-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1991-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Dickey, Kim, General, 1988-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Dillingham, James Richard, General, 1981-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Di Pasqua, Paul, General, 1990-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - di Rosa, Veronica, General, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Donoghue, John, General, 1980-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - D'Onofrio, Bernard, General, 1989-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Duckworth, Ruth, Archival Resource Key (Box 4)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, 1989-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Biographies, Résumés, 1994, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Collector Records, 1989-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Consignment Records, 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1987-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23-25)
    - Inventory and Price Lists, 1989-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Printed Material, 1988-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Shipping Records, 1989-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Photograph of Duckworth, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1988-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Earl, Jack, Archival Resource Key (Box 4)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1990-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Collector Records, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Consignment Records (other galleries), 1990-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Price Lists, 1989-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Printed Material, 1978-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Shipping Records, 1991-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Writings, circa 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 39-41)
  - Eastman, Ken, General, 1990-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Einfalt, Linda, Archival Resource Key (Box 5)
    - General, 1984-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1984-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Ennis, Elizabeth, General, 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Engel, Mary, General, 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Ernst, Hedi-Katharina, General, 1995-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Erteman, Kathy, General, 1983-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Eslick, Susan, General, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Fang, Marvin Minto, General, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Federighi, Christine, General, 1978-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Feldman, Bella Tabak, General, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Fenci, Piero, General, 1978-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Fenicchia, Concetta, General, 1983-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Fisar, Marek, General, 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Fleming, Carol, General, 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Fletcher, Sean A., General, 1997-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Fogarty, Jim, General, 1983-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Frey, Barbara L., General, circa 1990-1994, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Fritz, Donald C., General, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Fukazawa, Keiko, General, 1987-1988, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Furman, David, General, 1990-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes photograph of Furman.
  - Gill, John, Archival Resource Key (Box 5)
    - General, circa 1986-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1986-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Goodwin-Guerrero, Erin, General, 1986-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Grebe, Robin, General, 1991-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Griffith, Laura, General, 1996-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Griffith, Robert, Archival Resource Key (Box 5)
    - General, 1993-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1993-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Grimm, Jane B., General, circa 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Gronborg, Erik, General, circa 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Gudjonsdottir, Kristin, General, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Haas, Amanda, General, 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Hafner, Dorothy, General, circa 1983-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Hashimoto, Barbara, General, 1998-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Heid, Thomas, General, 1982-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Heikoop, Govert, General, 1992-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Hepburn, Tony, Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1986-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
    - Printed Material, 1978-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6)
      Oversized poster housed in OV 21.
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Hilferty, Patrick, General, 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Hobson, Charles, Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
    - General, 1993-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1993-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Hoch, Deborah, General, 1988-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Holcomb, Jan, General, 1978, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Honda, Shingo, General, 1988-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Hope, Linda, General, 1991-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Hovig-Schiltz, Kate, General, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16)